chinafile.com 2002-04-02

# SinoFile.net - China Business Matrix - China's premier media monitoring company

**Your Privacy**  
At SinoFile.net we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information collected to process orders and provide a more personalized browsing experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What about "cookies"?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features and to store items that help us assist you when you revisit our site. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. If you choose to not use cookies, some information retrieval may become less convenient, but every effort will be made to get you what you need based on "cookie-less" sessions.

**Will SinoFile.net disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
SinoFile.net does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. SinoFile.net may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but These statistics will include no personally identifying information. SinoFile.net may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of SinoFile.net, our users, or others.

**In summary**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make our site better and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Your consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SinoFile.net. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
